<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Meghana Bio Seeds</string>

    <string name="dialog_action_ok">OK</string>
    <!--<string name="dialog_action_cancel">Cancel</string>-->
    <string name="dialog_error_title">Sorry</string>

    <!-- Detail Activity -->
    <!--<string name="text_pokemon_id">Id: %s</string>-->
    <!--<string name="text_pokemon_name">Name: %s</string>-->
    <!--<string name="text_pokemon_experience">Experience: %s</string>-->

    <!-- Error View -->
    <string name="error_title">Oops</string>
    <string name="error_message">There was a problem loading the pokemon, please try again!</string>
    <string name="error_reload">Reload</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps_sample">Map</string>
    <string name="error_something_bad_happened">Something bad happened. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="about_us">Meghana group has come a long way since it was started by Shri M.Krishna Murthy in May,2009 in his native village Nakrekal, Nalgonda dist of Telangana state. Meghana group which began with the vision to transform village agriculture by promoting innovative agri-rich bio products among village farmers in Indian condition.
        By God's grace, thanks to the vision and dynamic leadership of it's founder, Meghana group today has successfully established itself as one of the leading names in pesticides promoters in Telangana, Andhra Pradesh and Karnataka, creating accepted awareness among the farming community about the benefits of the products.
        Meghana Group promoters bring with them vast experience in the agriculture field. The founder Shri M.Krishna Murthy is an Agriculture Graduate from A.P Agriculture University, Bapatla. His service in the industry of agriculture pesticides, fertilizers, seeds and bioproducts is since August 3rd, 1984, started from M/S Sandoz India Ltd, Hyderabad. His service to the industry and farming community is worthable. Since, he is doing for the betterment of the farmers, in addition his son M. Vikram Sandeep Kumar who is working for the Department of agriculture, Telangana was post graduate in Agricultural Economics.</string>
</resources>
